Welcome back everybody.
For chance of Cenar.
I'm in the warrior domain.
Sneaking about.
And hopefully not getting caught.
Let's see here.
Where am I supposed to go?
Probably just hide around here.
These guys are facing the other way.
How am I gonna make it across there?
So people are gonna appear on the left.
Are they gonna see me if I hurry?
Uh-oh, uh-oh.
Shit.
Okay, this guy's turning around.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
There's something over there.
Oh, don't turn around, don't turn around.
Oh, shit.
Oh, shit!
Crap, the thing!
Oh, no!
I got sliced!
Okay, so he's gonna see me if I do that.
That ain't good.
How can I avoid that?
Ah, I see.
I use this as cover, of course.
Of course.
I didn't think about that.
Makes a lot of sense.
Let's wait.
God, I love the graphic style of this game.
The simplicity of it speaks to me.
I gotta make the thumbnail something like this, for sure.
I love the simple thumbnails.
Okay, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
Oh, that was close.
Okay, so I got something to distract people with now.
I throw here and I go over here.
But then this guy is gonna be okay.
So he walks back and forth, huh?
We can make that happen.
Also, I'm gonna wait for this guy to be in front.
Now.
Investigate, investigate.
Go!
Quick!
Oh, man.
Kinda crazy that there's stealth in this game.
Okay, so wait a minute.
We got some things here.
What's this?
Multiple something?
Plural?
Do I have any other glyphs that look like this?
Looks like a battle axe, almost.
Mid-swing.
So it's located here.
Maybe some kind of armory or something like that.
Okay, I'm gonna wait for this guy to go back over here and then I'm gonna go for it.
Oh, wait, there's also a staircase over here.
Shit!
Okay, go, go, go, go, go, go.
I think I'm gonna wait one more time just to be sure.
I'm scared.
I don't want to get caught.
And even though there are no real repercussions for getting caught, I'm still afraid.
Thank God they can't hear my footsteps.
Yo!
I'm a fucking god!
I called it, didn't I?
Armory!
Yo!
What the hell are the chances of that?
That was a pure guess.
Shot in the dark.
Yo, I can arm myself?
You're kidding!
Oh, I see what's gonna happen here.
I'm gonna blend in.
I need armor though.
Uh, helmet is... give me a big helmet.
I like that.
We gotta get one of these instead, yeah.
And then maybe... what is this stuff?
Bracers?
But I don't look like a soldier at all!
I need the actual armor.
Okay, let's see how this goes.
Ah, shit!
Ah, they immediately saw through my disguise.
I mean, obviously, look at me.
This is a pathetic attempt.
Perhaps the rest of the armory is to the north.
Ah, shit!
I did not expect him to be right there when I exited.
That's unfortunate.
Let's try again.
Be ready to get back in.
Shit!
No!
Okay, I'm not sure what I'm supposed to do here.
Ah, hmm.
I mean, is there anything else I can do over there?
Did I miss something obvious here?
How about we grab a shield as well?
Why not?
That looks fancy, right?
Maybe a small helmet instead?
No, I like the big helmet.
Big helmet is good.
Let's try it now.
Are you gonna notice me?
Shit!
Ah, no, the guy is coming through the door!
I'm terrible at this game.
Okay, now go out here.
Hopefully he's not standing in the same position.
Nope, he's still there.
Oh, no.
What else can I do?
This is the only thing to click on.
That's weird.
Am I supposed to outrun them somehow?
Or fight them?
I mean, I have a weapon.
Run!
No!
What?
I don't know.
Uh, put him back, maybe?
Let's just revert back to the original clothes.
Just undo everything we did in here.
Okay, so he immediately sees me.
I cannot sneak past him.
Why is he not patrolling back and forth as he did before, though?
That's the question.
He's always in that same position, right?
Yeah, look, he's always on the right.
Don't get me!
This is a real tough one!
I am pretty lost here.
Oh, I hate when they chase me!
Get away from me!
I'm so bad at this game, it's wild.
Okay, lock in.
Think.
So, we're in here.
We can't leave.
There's things to put on.
We can change the outfit, but there's no chestplate.
So, what the hell, man?
I can tell already, this is gonna be one of those puzzles that I will be inexplicably stuck on.
And then when I finally solve it, I'm gonna feel really dumb.
I mean, I feel dumb already!
Don't hit me at the head.
Uh, man.
What else can I click on here?
Anything in the boxes?
Maybe they love boxes, right?
Maybe I bring them a present, I've wrapped a gift.
The fact that I can combine these different armor pieces has to mean something, right?
It's the whole point of this room.
Let's really lock in and think about this.
Maybe they hate certain helmets.
Do you like this helmet?
They hate this helmet!
Am I soft-locked here?
What's happening?
What am I supposed to do?
Uh, help?
Hilfe?
Oh, it's like the tutorials, I guess.
No, I don't want any help!
I want to figure this out!
These bastards are giving me nightmares!
Okay, let's really super lock in.
Okay, what can we click on?
Did I miss something super basic in here?
Let's just take a step back.
Let's look at this again.
So we got the shield.
A nice shield, it's looking real fine.
Bracers, yeah.
Do we have anything about...
shields in here?
Maybe I have to wear a certain combination of items.
What is he wearing?
Headguard, shoulders...
This guy has a shield.
And a hat.
Maybe I just try that.
Shield and a hat.
Uh, get rid of this spear.
Hey, what do you think of this?
You don't think much of it.
Oh wait, I'm so stupid!
I gotta look like them!
Uh, wait, wait, go back out, I need to have another look.
Okay, so they have big hats, sword, bracers.
Oh my god, if this is it.
Okay, uh, big hat?
Uh, sword?
Bracers.
I swear to god if this is it.
Oh my god!
I'm so dumb.
This has to mean weapon, right?
Oh, you know what, it looks like a battle axe, what did I say before?
Weapon.
It's a weapon.
And this is weapons.
Incredible.
By far the hardest puzzle in this game so far.
Languages?
Not a problem.
As simple as this, guys.
I can't do it, Captain.
It's too much.
Oh, so now I can just walk through here, no problem.
Oh, so nice.
That is wonderful!
Oh, what a reward.
You know what, it was worth all the time investment.
This is great.
Can I fall in line with these guys?
I wanna march with them, so I can walk through the door at the end.
Maybe I can't.
They're not gonna mind me at all?
Hey, don't mind me!
I've just lost!
Uh, let's go... let's...
Oh, I can't follow them in there, unfortunately.
I'm going downstairs.
Okay.
So we're back here.
Let me see.
Carry the little crate.
Now we know all the words.
I think maybe there's one word I haven't gotten yet.
So he says carry the big crate.
At some point he says something that I don't quite understand, I think.
There we go.
And now he says...
Yeah, go to the cart.
But we haven't done these through the book yet.
Lay the crates.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, we got it.
We got it.
Now, how do I get back...
Oh, I just walked down, I guess.
Now that I have the disguise...
I look so out of place.
Oh, wait a sec!
Is that for getting the elevator back up?
Hmm...
I think so, and then it falls down.
When I pull this... yeah, I see.
It's like a counterweight.
But what about this door?
Okay, that's where I was before, I believe.
Yeah, this is the boxes and sippy cups.
I'm going upstairs now.
These guys are not going to mind me, are they?
I'm assuming that in one of the other locations I'm going to be wearing a different set of armor.
The fact that there were multiple combinations of it, right?
Okay, so these guys are looking just like me, that's good.
Don't mind me.
Just exploring.
I'm going to go up north here now.
Uh, yeah, keep going.
Move the camera!
There we go.
Now go up north.
Are they going to chase me here?
This looks oddly similar to the first level of the tower.
You know, they also had these canals.
Warrior God.
Okay.
So we know a cart.
Where is it?
This one.
It even looks like a cart.
That's funny.
Now weapon.
Warrior God?
Could be Warrior Leader.
It's a leader for sure.
Yeah.
Duty, okay.
That one I did not expect at all.
So the duty of the warriors, is that what he's saying?
He says carry the weapon.
Warrior's duty?
To carry the weapon.
Push doors?
Oh, I probably got that one wrong, huh?
Oh, is it push carts?
Oh no, it wouldn't be.
Something, something, something.
So they have multiple tasks.
Carry weapon.
So what do these warriors do?
They carry boxes, they push carts, and they carry weapons.
What else do they do?
They march.
Push something?
I must have gotten the door wrong then, right?
Let's see here.
Yeah, see, door, I'm not sure about the door part.
Which ones did I not get yet?
This one.
What does this one mean?
You know, he's protecting these smaller children or whatever.
Maybe their duty is to protect.
Yo, what if it turns out these warriors are not actually bad guys at all?
That's what I've been thinking, right?
Given the whole area we're in, the rivers made of blood, I think so at least.
You know, they seem evil in a way.
But maybe they are actually just protecting the devotees and all the others.
Perhaps God is not all they think he is.
Maybe God is something very sinister.
Oh, that would be a nice twist actually.
And look at this, demons and angels or whatever.
Yeah, oh, there's two of them.
Oh, okay, so angel and demon.
I didn't notice this.
Let's see here.
Warrior, this guy has a shield and a spear.
This guy has the big helmet, the sword and the bracers I imagine.
Oh, wait, is he saying the three things?
The warrior carries the duty.
The warrior does what?
So this big block represents duty.
Oh, it's so literal as well.
The warrior literally carries the duty, right?
That's funny.
Here the warrior does what exactly?
Stands guard.
What's happening here?
The warrior pushes...
pushes what?
Did I get push correct?
I'm pretty sure it did.
Yeah, push is correct.
Yeah, because there's no question mark on it, obviously.
Door is wrong for sure.
What are they pushing here?
Looks more like they're reaching for the sky, you know, hands up!
And they're like, oh, don't shoot me.
I mean, the glyph itself has its arms up.
You know, looks like a man.
I'm going to go out on a limb here and say this is...
person or man.
Is that crazy?
Now this right here.
Warrior...
Actually, you know what?
Let me put man or...
What did I have before?
Door.
Man push...
Door, right?
So I don't think it's any of those, but who knows?
Warrior guards slash protects something.
We also have this guy here that we didn't get.
So this is stop.
Go.
Well, I'm not sure about these, right?
But let's also, again, take a look at the actual shape of this.
Remember I said that it could have been this one because it has sort of the same arrow shape?
Turns out it wasn't this one.
Oh, actually, it was this one I meant the other time.
But perhaps there's another one.
Like that one.
I'm not sure what that means yet, though.
And I don't want to guess.
Okay, warrior's duty.
So they're basically chanting, I guess, the three duties of the warrior that we saw in the very beginning of this place.
Hey, where am I now?
Weapons.
Yeah, armory.
Ooh, look at this over here.
A huge sword!
Warriors.
Stop.
Something.
Men.
Hold back death.
Hmm.
Let's go down there and check it out.
What do we have here?
Something, something.
Also, we got a couple new here.
This thing.
Yeah, I'm not sure what that is yet.
Let's go in here and see what this place is.
Oh, that is beautiful looking.
Love the camera angles and...
The feeling of distance is real in this game.
Look at this, some kind of arena.
Or theater.
What's going on down there?
Lizard!
I wonder if I have to translate that at some point.
The word for lizard?
In the warrior's language.
Oh man, this place is so cool.
In the beginning, when I came here, I definitely preferred the look of the first area, but now I'm actually not so sure.
I really like the signs of both of these areas.
This one is way more large in scope, right?
And more imposing.
Just look at my character looking around up, because it's such a huge area.
Okay, what is this?
Ooh!
We got weights, a ship, a musical instrument, and a key.
Oh, we're back to the four things.
What were the four things?
Vase?
Instrument?
And then we had...
Key?
And the last one...
was...
I forgot, dammit.
Uh, sword.
Sword.
What's this?
Oh, which one is more important?
Oh, that's a good question.
I don't know.
In the first area, it was kind of easy, right?
Because we had...
devotees, men, preacher, and God, right?
And they all had like...
It was like a hierarchy of status.
And that makes sense, I guess.
Yeah, I'm not sure about this one.
We definitely got to do this in the correct order.
We got to ring these bells.
Okay.
I can't help but...
think about Silent Hill when I see this helmet.
Oh!
I love bottles.
What was this?
What's inside?
Oh!
Hmm, this could mean eye.
I love bottles.
I mean, they do love their bottles, right?
They also love their crates.
They love that stuff.
And here's a book on...
those bells.
Is that my face?
Or is that someone else?
Because I'm wearing a helmet.
Oh, that's creepy.
That's really creepy.
That's a bench.
I think this one means eye.
Or me.
Me.
Oh, we also got something up here.
Does that make sense, though?
That there's a sign called me?
Me love bottle.
Hmm.
Who could love bottles?
Someone with a specific name.
Yeah,
and I can't do this right here.
Maybe I gotta bring this guy a bottle.
And he will open up the door.
I see him inside.
It's creepy as hell.
Oh, man.
And then he will give me the combination to those bells.
Is that the right word for those things?
Isn't there another word for a bell that is really big and used in towers?
There's a word for a tower like that.
What is this?
Plural something.
What is in here?
Whoa.
All right.
I'm intrigued by that.
Are those...
humans?
Devotees?
No, no, no.
Never mind.
These are all the soldiers.
Look at that.
Oh.
We carry musical instruments?
Who is it that carries that?
Who is this person?
Wait a second now.
Who is that person?
I've seen this person before.
Oh, man.
Look at that guy.
Trampling skulls?
That's horrific.
Warrior not fear death, maybe?
Let's assume it means fear.
Fear or a cause?
Warrior not cause death?
Then again...
I mean, he's clearly causing death.
He's trampling on top of skulls.
So maybe that's a bad assumption.
Warrior does not what?
Death.
What does the warrior not do?
Hmm.
I don't know.
Keep it on fear for now.
He's trampling on skulls.
This guy is presenting a sword.
The warrior carries a weapon.
I mean, these obviously are the three things that they were chanting in the other room.
The drill sergeant.
We march on our forefathers.
I don't know.
We play music.
I mean, they love music.
Music is apparently something very divine in this world, right?
Oh, look at these guys.
They have shields and spears.
So are they going to chase me when I get over here?
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Warriors stop.
What are you stopping?
Also, what is this place supposed to be?
Warriors...
Stop...
And then plural something.
What are they preventing?
Hmm.
That is interesting.
Let me look at my notes again.
See if I don't have a picture of that dude.
Yeah, look, there he is.
Musical instrument and everything.
It's the same.
Oh, it's just now occurring to me.
These guys in front are not the focus.
It's this dude.
Warrior push.
What is the warrior push?
Wait a minute.
The warrior carries the duty.
That's not the same as this.
This is the warrior carries the sword.
Is it not?
Yeah, carries a weapon.
Okay, so never mind.
These three are not the same as what we have here.
That's what I thought.
That's not the case.
I mean, obviously, I gotta go back to the beginning at some point.
Because I've gained all this knowledge here.
Obviously, I'll be able to connect some dots, huh?
I'll be back.
Yeah, let's just keep going this way again.
And try and see if we can't find a bottle for this dude.
Very pretty music playing right here for a place as sinister as this.
And now it's gone.
I love this vista, if you can even call it that.
Damn.
It also seems to be perpetual night up here.
And if you remember the murals from the very beginning of the game...
The night sky was actually depicted as...
Well, night.
At some point when the warriors were on, right?
So I don't even know what to call this place.
I would love to fill this out, but I can't tell what that place is even after having been there.
Let's explore this sword a bit more.
So liberating being able to explore freely with this disguise.
Oh, that is beautiful, though.
Yeah, so whatever this says is the same thing that those warriors were saying...
In front of the door just before.
So... men...
stop death.
Warriors...
stop something that in turn...
causes men to stop death.
What could that mean?
Let's think about this in terms of nouns and adjectives and shit.
Because you start with the noun, warrior, right?
Verb... stops slash halts.
So now we need a noun.
Actually, more like adjective and then a noun at the end.
Because plural something.
Multiple warriors or warriors...
stop...
evil...
God.
Maybe God is evil.
Nah, I don't know.
I have no clue.
Bottles!
Hey!
Let's check that out.
Take me to bottle factory.
Lizard!
It's kind of cute.
Oh!
Oh, nice shortcut.
Well, let's go grab a bottle if we can.
Can I actually just go over there and grab one?
I think I can.
Hey, guys, I'm one of you now.
Don't worry about...
Oh, okay, you don't like me doing that.
That's fine.
I can go in here.
Sorry.
Yeah, get out of the way.
I need a sippy cup.
You know how it is.
Give me that.
Yeah!
Nice!
A wonderful sippy cup.
See, now it looks like a proper bottle up close.
But from here, tell me that doesn't look like a sippy cup...
for little kids.
Hahaha!
Alright, let's just get back up there and hand over this cup...
or bottle.
The guy's gonna go mad nuts for it, probably.
And perhaps he will also spill the secrets of the universe for us.
I look so out of place when I run around and do this.
It's crazy to me that they haven't noticed anything off.
Look at all these different lizards.
There's so many of them.
Okay, a nice shortcut to bottles.
By the way, all these little platforms here now make me think there's an elevator going to that spot.
Do you see how the dots are the same on the elevator?
Are we gonna have elevators going everywhere?
That's what I think.
Okay, back up.
Up to the dude that loves bottles.
Maybe he's like an outcast or a hermit.
Because he lives a little bit off the beaten path, right?
By himself.
And he loves the bottle.
He loves getting drunk.
I'm assuming there's alcohol in here.
Who knows?
Okay.
Excuse me.
I can see you.
Oh, right.
I don't know what to do.
Hey, check this out.
Oh, wait.
Do I need two bottles?
Let's look inside.
Are you gonna take the bottle?
You bastard.
Let's leave.
Ah!
Aha!
Look at him!
He's just chilling up there.
Looking at the night sky.
Who are you?
Sir, do you mind if I sneak in here?
Quietly?
What's this?
Oh!
I love it already!
Something duty.
Something something.
This is the same word in all of these.
Look.
Oh, my God.
Okay, okay, okay.
Calm yourself.
What's going on here?
Oh, my goodness.
Yeah, this is going to be tough.
Which one am I missing here?
I have a feeling I should be able to do this one.
Or this one, at least, right?
Stop.
March.
What else is related to that?
Stop.
March.
Maybe follow.
Yeah, okay, but that doesn't help me.
I don't know which symbol it is, right?
Yeah.
Is there anything else I can click on in here?
Okay, so the dude is occupied up there, just chilling with the bottle.
And he loves the bottle.
In the meantime, we're going to go back to the very beginning, because I want to see those early stages again.
And get those hints from the game.
Most likely, when we figure out some of the early stuff, the rest of the puzzle is going to click, you know?
All the pieces are going to fall into their rightful places.
Or however you say that.
You know what I mean.
This area right here reminds me a little bit of a certain area in Tunic.
If you've played the game, you probably know what I'm talking about.
Can I go over here?
I cannot.
What about down here?
I saw something here.
Yeah, so where does this lead?
Aha!
What's happening up here?
Excuse me?
You're just repeating the same thing that was on the sword, sir.
Me... stop, halt, bottle?
Okay, I think I got the stop slash halt wrong.
Maybe that means... me...
hate the bottle?
Maybe he hates the bottle?
The other guy loves it?
Maybe this guy hates it?
I don't know.
Why would I have called that one stop?
That's why I need to go back to the beginning.
And they're laughing.
Let me through.
Okay, I thought maybe they were going to prevent me from going through, but...
interesting.
Are they laughing at me because I'm not carrying a bottle up here?
Aw, man, look at that!
Love this style!
And look at this, it's the same tower, of course, that we saw from the outside in the other place.
Oh, look, it's an observatory!
Yo!
I love that!
We got books and shit?
Oh, God, I love this!
I love this!
What's here?
Lovely music, too.
Oh, what does that mean?
The seal of someone.
This is a name, for sure.
Or maybe a rank.
You know, like the royal stamp, or the royal decree.
I don't know.
Also, we have this symbol.
That is a similar symbol that we saw in the church.
On the first level of the tower.
There's something up here.
Ah, something is missing.
Something star-shaped.
Let's have a peek!
Ah, beautiful!
Look at that!
Can I click on any of these?
It's got to be a puzzle here somehow, right?
Oh, fun fact!
You see how these stars have these so-called diffraction spikes on them?
Right here.
They're not real.
It's like an artifact in the image, caused by light diffracting around the support beams holding up the secondary mirror of a reflecting telescope.
You can actually simulate that with your own eyes.
Just squint at a really bright source, and your eyelids will function as the support beams where light diffracts around it.
Okay, so this is definitely the Earth.
We got the Moon and the Sun.
Or whatever you want to call the Earth in this world, and the Moon and the Sun, right?
Or God.
Oh, where is it?
There it is.
Sun slash God, right?
I'm going to assume God.
Let's just call this Moon to be super simple about it.
And...
No, these were the two only ones.
And look at here, yeah.
Sun, Earth, Moon.
I mean, if we assume Solar System.
Yeah, look at this.
Sun.
Oh, but what is this here?
Moon.
Yes.
Someone ringing a bell.
Did I note something down with bells?
Well, we do have a name for a bell, maybe.
We did encounter four bells earlier, remember?
What looks like a bell?
Maybe that one?
A little bit?
I'm not sure.
These are definitely correct.
I wonder what their obsession is with crates and bottles.
Maybe it's just like a standard warrior setup, you know?
Warriors love alcohol because it gets boring out in the field.
They love boxes because that's how they carry around their grenades and weapons and all that.
I don't know.
Supplies, right?
For war.
Not sure.
Heaven and hell.
Heaven and hell, angels and demons.
Protection.
But I don't know which ones.
Go there, right?
I could imagine this simple meaning protect.
Because the guy is standing there with a shield, right?
In fact, this even looks a little bit like a shield.
If you stretch the imagination a bit.
Let's do shield slash protect.
Actually, it should be protect because we're dealing with a verb here, right?
Noun, verb, noun, most likely.
What do the warriors protect?
They protect this thing.
And that thing, have we seen that anywhere else?
Do they protect the bell?
Hmm.
Maybe they do.
Warrior carries the duty.
The warrior pushes something that is incorrect right now, for sure.
Man slash door is incorrect.
If this means push, maybe this means pull.
Or poop and suck.
We got to find something star-shaped and put it in here.
And then presumably slide this into the telescope.
And you know what will happen?
It's going to highlight one of the stars for me.
One of those stars are going to be significant somehow.
I don't know how or why, but it's going to happen.
Oh, actually, wait a minute.
What was this simple again?
On the table.
Okay.
All right, let's get going.
Also, just to add to what I was talking about before with the diffraction spikes.
You may see a couple of things when you squint your eyes and create a very tiny slit.
Light will diffract and create a diffraction pattern too, and you can see that with your own eyes.
It's exactly the same thing that happens when you shine a laser through a diffraction grating.
If any of you have ever done that.
Look at me, I'm so tiny.
Okay.
Guys, guys, you need to speak to me.
The warrior stops something.
And the man stops...
Well, this could also be something else.
What could something stop something else?
Leader, perhaps, or...
Yo, what if...
No, never mind.
I was about to say something really dumb.
Me stop slash halt bottle.
Maybe he says me need bottle, and I gotta go get him a bottle.
Why are they laughing?
He says something and then they both laugh.
Maybe he says I want bottle and they're both like, ha ha ha, yeah, we want bottles, we want to get drunk.
Is that what that means?
Where's my symbol for that?
Stop halt?
I mean, what else could it be?
Think about it.
It is... Which one is it?
That one.
Stop, go pass, but then again, I could be wrong about these.
But I think I'm pretty right.
I mean...
That's what they're doing, right?
They're stopping, halting, and then they pass and go.
I can go down here, maybe.
Yay!
Yes, I can.
Oh?
Ah, this is that simple that we saw on the... on the...
on the desk.
The astronomer.
You know what?
Maybe that means astronomer, actually.
Let's be super simple-minded about this.
Let's say that means astronomer.
In fact, this even looks like a prism with light coming into the prism.
You see what I mean?
Light coming in, being refracted?
I don't know.
Maybe that's a stretch.
Not to be confused with diffraction.
I'm talking about refraction.
Different phenomenon.
Yo, oh, oh, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Get in line, get in line.
He's carrying a note.
Warrior, lay your weapon?
Oh, sorry.
Sorry, I'm not allowed to have weapons in there.
You got it.
There we go.
Sorry, sorry.
What did you say before?
Say it again.
Now you can go?
Thank you.
Okay, I need to wait, then.
Maybe it means move.
I mean, it's the same thing as go, I guess, right?
I'm gonna add that to the thing.
Go, move.
Like, move out, soldiers, right?
That would be something a drill sergeant would say, or a leader of a squad.
Okay, now we get in line here.
No weapon allowed.
Is this guy wearing a stick?
No, it's also a sword.
It was just the angle.
So what is that note he's carrying?
I totally look out of place.
My helmet is wrong, too.
Whoa.
Boxes and bottles.
Carry the... You got it.
Oh, shit.
Sorry, sorry.
What?
Huh?
I'm what I do.
What I do.
What I do?
Oh, my God.
I didn't do nothing.
Okay, put the sword over here.
Just like that.
Maybe I have to wait until it's my turn.
I thought maybe he wanted me to do it from the beginning.
Getting inside vibes from this one now.
If you know what I mean.
Okay, okay, let's wait.
Oh, and the last one in the queue.
Carry the big crate.
Okay, so he goes over there, grabs the crate.
Little crate.
Is he gonna say bottle?
You got it.
Yeah, exactly.
Warriors move.
Dude, this game is awesome.
I love this shit.
Look at these shadows, too.
That's so satisfying.
Oh, we gotta put them on the cart now.
Ah, here we go.
Lay the crate.
This is wonderful.
He says, move now.
Notice he said it in singular.
Lay the crate.
And then they walk over there.
Okay.
Okay, not yet, not yet.
Let's wait.
We follow orders here.
Boom.
Don't run, you maniac.
Just walk normally.
Warrior, push the troll.
You got it!
Oh, shit!
Here we go.
What's he doing with it?
Okay, okay, can I just...
I'm gonna go down here now, if you don't mind.
Yo, okay!
The warriors came from the sea.
And they saw the tower in the distance.
And they were enchanted by the music.
Musicians.
This could mean tower.
Or travel.
Let's say tower or travel.
Or sailing.
Or boat, you know, something like that.
Journey, perhaps.
Ah, man, I love this.
They love the music.
There was music.
Musicians.
Musician.
That's what that is.
Right?
And what happened then?
Then they built a wall?
Built wall?
No way.
Built...
Um, let me see, how does that look?
That one.
Wall or...
It could also be fortification.
I guess.
So they saw these musicians, they liked it so much.
They decided to join them and protect them.
By building a wall.
Oh.
The duty is to protect everyone against the evils.
Mandor is wrong, I think Mandor is...
Demon.
It's got to be demon, right?
That's so awesome.
Oh, and check this out.
Now we're going to go in here.
These are demons!
These are the musicians!
Brother.
Oh, this is great.
The fraction great.
Protect.
Fortification.
Right?
Demon.
Where's my musician?
No way, it's wrong!
I think these two are correct.
That one is incorrect.
So, what is he doing here?
He's saying...
Stop.
He's totally protecting them, right?
Musicians and demons.
Or, you know what?
Instead of musicians, we could call them angels.
Because look at them, they're also floating in the air, right?
Yeah.
Let's call this angels.
We're going to have both.
This could also be enemy.
Demons are enemies.
Like that.
And their duty is to protect...
the citizens of the tower against the evil abroad.
Except I got that one wrong, so...
I have a word for protector that I thought was protected.
Let's try.
Oh, no way!
Okay.
I guess this is more akin to protection than building a wall.
Impure.
Okay, I did not see that coming.
Very interesting.
Maybe they consider the inhabitants on the level below them the chosen ones.
You know what?
This actually reminds me a lot of the story of the people from the first level.
In that case, God was shining so harshly that all the plants died.
And then they found this tower...
So they actually came later, I guess.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
So the warriors found God first.
They found this tower first.
Right?
They loved the music.
They decided to protect it at all costs.
Then later on...
the...
people, normal people, non-warriors came.
And they were denied entrance to the upper levels, I guess.
Yeah.
So we get a timeline here of sorts.
Now, the first one here is...
I'm not sure about that.
These could mean stars, actually.
Right?
Look at that.
These guys have these symbols behind them, too.
It's very prevalent.
Chosen ones.
Tower of the chosen ones.
I think this one is not correct right now.
I'm going to say travel is one option.
But it could also mean...
stars...
or God.
I'm not sure.
That is cool.
Yeah, the duty.
Ah, cool.
Look at those demons right there.
What is down here?
More lizards?
I knew these guys weren't evil.
They love music.
How can you be evil when you love music?
Yeah, look at this.
Sailing.
Music.
Key.
And scales.
Scales of justice, perhaps.
Oh.
It's a light.
Oh, cool.
Oh, I'm going to put the light inside of here.
It's going to shine through these little panels.
And show me something on the walls.
Watch.
Oh, never mind.
I was so sure of that.
Oh, what the...
Interesting.
What's this?
Okay, it's a ship, yeah.
Maybe I change my mind now on this guy right here.
Instead of travel, let's call it ship or boat.
But what is happening with these little things on the floor?
Oh, it's just a place to put it, I guess, if I need to.
Very weird.
Let me see this over here.
I thought for sure the light would reveal something extra.
But I guess not.
Then again, look at this right side of the instrument.
Almost looks like a key.
Doesn't it?
Astronomer.
You know what?
I may be wrong about that.
It could also be light.
Starlight.
I mean, that's what astronomers do, right?
They pass light through a prism.
That's spectroscopy, baby.
Look at this here.
Elevator?
I don't have what it takes, it seems.
Need some kind of item for that.
Ah, fast travel!
Nice!
Do we get to have a Zoom meeting?
Okay.
Yep.
Five balls.
This I'm very unsure of.
What the frick?
Huh?
What does that mean?
By the way, this dude right here, is this God?
Is he speaking to all the different cultures in the Tower of Babel?
Maybe he's the one who gave them the language.
Right?
I mean, the Tower of Babel, for those that don't know, is the story of God, sort of...
Giving all the different cultures of the world different languages so they can't really communicate with each other and stuff like that.
So maybe there's something there going on, I mean...
He kind of looks like a god, right?
Or a noir detective.
He just needs a cigarette and a drink.
And some jazz music.
All right!
Well, break time!
I'll see you in the next one.
Thank you so much for watching, and bye-bye.